https://www.sigmapro.com/privacy_statement

PRIVACY STATEMENT FOR SIGMAPRO.COM
SigmaPro is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the SigmaPro site and governs data collection and usage. By using the SigmaPro site, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
SigmaPro collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number. SigmaPro also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by SigmaPro. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by SigmaPro for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the SigmaPro site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through SigmaPro public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: SigmaPro does not read any of your private online communications.
SigmaPro encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from SigmaPro so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. SigmaPro is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the SigmaPro Web site.
Use of your Personal Information
SigmaPro collects and uses your personal information to operate the SigmaPro website and deliver the services you have requested. SigmaPro also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from SigmaPro and its affiliates. SigmaPro may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
SigmaPro does not sell, rent, or lease its customer lists to third parties. SigmaPro may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, SigmaPro may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to SigmaPro, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.  SigmaPro does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
SigmaPro tracks pages our customers visit within the SigmaPro website in order to determine what SigmaPro services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within SigmaPro to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
SigmaPro will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SigmaPro or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SigmaPro; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SigmaPro or the public.
Use of Cookies
The SigmaPro website use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a webpage server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize SigmaPro pages, or register with  the SigmaPro site or services, a cookie helps SigmaPro recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same SigmaPro website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the SigmaPro features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the SigmaPro services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
SigmaPro secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. SigmaPro secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
SigmaPro will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. SigmaPro encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how SigmaPro is protecting your information.
Contact Information
SigmaPro welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that SigmaPro has not adhered to this Statement, please contact SigmaPro at webmaster <at> sigmapro <dot> com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
